Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/bhavinpatel2022 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Corporate Finance Structured Finance Finance

Languages

English

Gujarati

Hindi

Spanish (Elementary)

Bhavin Patel

CEO, LenDenClub Platforms Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Summary

True to my roots of being a quintessential Gujarati, I am positively stereotypical in my entrepreneurial approach. I co-founded LenDenClub in 2015 with a vision of having an enhanced investor experience. Despite not being blessed with top B-school credentials and experience from the big giants, I am a go-getter, bullish, very desi, ROI minded and like to understand the consumers by the pulse.

I brought P2P in India and I didn't believe in running after seed funding - I first built the base and only then approached for seed funding. There is no success with shortcuts and this belief of mine makes me an advocate of hard work, discipline and integrity.

Discipline comes from my sports background and love for sports - an avid football player and has in fact found my LenDenClub cofounder through football itself - Dipesh, with whom I played and still play football. This culture of football has thus been instilled amongst every LenDenite through a positive reinforcement of participation every Thursday post work. I religiously play football every Sunday with my circle at 4 in the morning.

I am passionate about what I do, whether it's work, football, fitness or love for mobiles & cars. Hierarchy is never a yardstick for me and I prefer being emphatic and equal in my day-to-day interactions with team members whether a GET/MT or my Co-Founder.

I've learnt from my experiences immensely, far more than what books could've taught me. And it's only fair to pass on what you get. My ambition is not just to be a successful entrepreneur but I yearn to be a contributor to the nation by disrupting the FinTech space.

Experience

LenDenClub
Founder | CEO
September 2014 - Present (10 years 8 months)
Mumbai Area, India

Being Human Clothing

AVP - Finance (Fund Raise)

October 2013 - October 2014 (1 year 1 month)

Electronica Finance Limited
Sr. Manager - Structured Finance
October 2011 - October 2013 (2 years 1 month)

SPAN Analytics Pvt Ltd.
Co-Founder
June 2009 - July 2011 (2 years 2 months)
Mumbai Area, India

Education

Kirloskar Institute of Advanced Management Studies (KIAMS) PGDM, Marketing & Finance

South Gujarat University
Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electronics & Communication